Finding Aid for the Mort Fine Papers PASC.0076
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Short stories, Articles, and Other Writings, 1945-1948
  - Booty From a Furlough - article, [1947] (Box 68)
  - Cajun Song - short story, [1947-1948] (Box 69)
  - Character sketches, 1946-1947 (Box 68)
  - Character sketches - Dick Rowe, no date (Box 68)
  - Day Justice Winked Her Eye (The) - article, no date (Box 68)
  - Don't Call Me Pop - short story, [1947] (Box 68)
  - Evening is Beautiful (The) - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - G.I. Lullaby -short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Home is Where the Heart Lies - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Huntress - short story, [1948] (Box 69)
  - If the Shoe Fits - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Jeff Bagnon, Detective - novel, no date (Box 68)
  - Johnny - short story, 1945 Nov (Box 69)
  - Journey Home - article, no date (Box 69)
  - Love Is For Today - short story, no date (Box 69)
  - Museum Piece - magazine story, [1948] (Box 66)
  - Museum Piece - magazine story, 1948 Feb 24 (Box 69)
  - My Heart Has Wings - short story, no date (Box 69)
  - Night Ride - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Novel, no date (Box 68)
  - October's Children - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Overnight Pass - short story, [1942-1944] (Box 69)
  - Pahrs' House - novel synopsis, no date (Box 68)
  - Peewee - short story, no date (Box 69)
  - Pending Outcome of the Story - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Plea for Intercultural Education (A) - article by Bernice Fine, no date (Box 68)
  - Relocation Center: Campus, U.S.A. - article, no date (Box 69)
  - Rise and Fall of the Roman Vampire (The) - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - So Little Time - short story, no date (Box 69)
  - Southbound Local - short story, [1945] (Box 69)
  - Strike - article, no date (Box 69)
  - Tomorrow Starts at Eight-Thirty - short story, 1946 Mar (Box 69)
  - Toti and Teina - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Two Ports in a Storm - short story, no date (Box 69)
  - Typescript manuscript (2 folders), no date (Box 69)
  - University of Pittsburgh English Assignments, 1945-1946 (Box 68)
  - Untitled short story, no date (Box 68)